Kael mss., 1939-2001 LMC 3004
Lilly Library
- II. Directors
  - Bogdanovich, Peter (Box 23)
    - The Last Picture Show., publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - Mask., (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Nickelodeon., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - Paper Moon., notes, clippings (Box 23)
    - Saint Jack., notes, clippings (Box 23)
    - Targets., publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - They All Laughed., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 23)
    - What's Up, Doc?, notes, publicity, press release, clippings (Box 23)
    - Notes and clippings concerning Bogdanovich (Box 23)
  - Boisset, Yves (Box 23)
    - L'Attentat (The Plot; The French Conspiracy - U.S.)., press kit, clippings (Box 23)
    - Dupont-Lajoie (Rape of Innocence - U.S.)., clippings (Box 23)
    - Un Taxi Mauve (The Purple Taxi - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 23)
  - Bondarchuk, Sergei (Box 23)
    - Voyna i mir (War and Peace - U.S.)., press release, clippings (Box 23)
    - clippings concerning other films (Box 23)
  - Boorman, John (Box 23)
    - Deliverance., notes, clippings (Box 23)
    - The Emerald Forest., (3 folders) (Box 23)
    - Excaliber., (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - The Exorcist II: The Heretic., notes, press release, press kit, clippings, 45rpm recording - Side I: "Pazuzo (Theme from the Exorcist II)" and Side II "Regan's Theme (Finale)" (Box 23)
    - Hell in the Pacific., program, press release (Box 23)
    - Hope and Glory., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 23)
    - Point Blank., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - Where the Heart Is., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 23)
    - Zardoz., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 23)
    - Clipping and printed item concerning Boorman (Box 23)
  - Borowczyk, Walerian and Jan Lenica (Box 23)
    - Dom., photographs, clippings (Box 23)
  - Borsos, Phillip (Box 23)
    - The Grey Fox., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - The Mean Season., (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - One Magic Christmas., (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Animator (Number 39, Fall 1986) concerning Borsos (Box 23)
  - Borzage, Frank (Box 23)
    - Desire., photographs (Box 23)
    - Little Man, What Now?, photographs (Box 23)
  - Boulting, John (Box 23)
    - Brighton Rock., notes, photographs (Box 23)
    - I'm All Right Jack., notes, clippings (Box 23)
  - Boulting, Roy (Box 23)
    - The Family Way., notes, clippings (Box 23)
    - There's a Girl in My Soup., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - Thunder Rock., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 23)
    - Materials concerning other films and Boulting brothers (Box 23)
  - Bourek, Zlatko (Box 23)
    - Bećarac (Dancing Songs - U.S.)., photographs (Box 23)
  - Bourguignon, Serge (Box 23)
    - clippings concerning various films (Box 23)
  - Bragaglia, Carlo L. (Box 23)
    - Lo Sbaglio di essere vivo (The Flesh Is Weak; The Widow and I - U.S.)., publicity, photographs (Box 23)
  - Brahm, John and Bretaigne Windust (Box 23)
    - Face to Face., photographs, clippings (Box 23)
  - Brandt, Henry and Heinz Sielmann (Box 23)
    - Les Seigneurs de la forêt (Masters of the Congo Jungle - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 23)
  - Braunberger, Pierre (Box 23)
    - La course de taureaux (Bullfight - U.S.)., (see also: Box 113) (Box 23)
  - Brealey, Gil (Box 23)
    - Annie's Coming Out (A Test of Love - U.S.)., press kit, clippings (Box 23)
  - Bresson, Robert (Box 23)
    - Au hazard Balthazar., photographs, clippings (Box 23)
    - Un condamnéà mort s'est échappé ou Le vent soufflé où il veut (A Man Escaped or: The Wind Bloweth Where It Listeth - U.S.)., notes, program, photographs, clippings (Box 23)
    - Une femme douce (A Gentle Woman - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 23)
    - Journal d'un cure de campagne (Diary of a Country Priest - U.S.)., programs, photographs, clippings (Box 23)
    - Procès de Jeanne d'Arc (Trial of Joan of Arc - U.S.)., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 23)
    - Quatre nuits d'un rêveur (Four Nights of a Dreamer - U.S.)., notes, press release, clippings (Box 23)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 23)
    - Notes, printed items and clippings concerning Bresson, (see also: Box 113) (Box 23)
  - Brest, Martin (Box 24)
    - Beverly Hills Cop., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Going in Style., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Hot Tomorrows., notes, clippings (Box 24)
    - Midnight Run., press kit, clippings (Box 24)
    - Simon., clippings (Box 24)
    - Men Don't Leave., notes, clippings (Box 24)
    - Risky Business., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 24)
  - Brickman, Marshall (Box 24)
    - Lovesick., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 24)
    - The Manhattan Project., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 24)
  - Bridges, Alan (Box 24)
    - The Return of the Soldier., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - The Shooting Party., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - clippings concerning other films (Box 24)
  - Bridges, James (Box 24)
    - Mike's Murder., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 24)
    - Urban Cowboy., notes, clippings (Box 24)
  - Brizzi, Gaëton, et al. (Box 24)
    - DuckTales: The Movie - Treasure of the Lost Lamp., press kit, clippings (Box 24)
  - Brook, Clive (Box 24)
    - On Approval., (2 folders) (see also: Box 113) (Box 24)
  - Brook, Peter (Box 24)
    - Beggar's Opera., notes, publicity, photographs, printed item, clippings (Box 24)
    - King Lear., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Lord of the Flies., press release, clippings (Box 24)
    - Marat/Sade., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Moderato Cantabile., notes, clippings (Box 24)
    - Tell Me Lies., notes, publicity, press release, clippings (Box 24)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 24)
    - Notes and clippings concerning Brook (Box 24)
  - Brooks, Albert (Box 24)
    - Defending Your Life., press kit, clippings (Box 24)
    - Lost in America., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 24)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Brooks (Box 24)
  - Brooks, James L. (Box 24)
    - Terms of Endearment., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Materials concerning Brooks (Box 24)
  - Brooks, Joseph (Box 24)
    - If I Ever See You Again., clippings (Box 24)
    - You Light Up My Life., notes, clippings (Box 24)
  - Brooks, Mel (Box 24)
    - Blazing Saddles., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - High Anxiety., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 24)
    - History of the World - Part I., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 24)
    - The Producers., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Silent Movie., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Spaceballs., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 24)
    - To Be or Not To Be., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 24)
    - Twelve Chairs., publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Young Frankenstein., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Brooks (Box 24)
  - Brooks, Richard (Box 24)
    - Crisis., photographs (Box 24)
  - Brown, Clarence (Box 24)
    - Flesh and the Devil., photographs (Box 24)
    - Intruder in the Dust., (see also: Box 113) (Box 24)
  - Browning, Tod (Box 24)
    - Freaks., (for publicity see also: Box 113) (Box 24)
    - Clippings and printed item concerning other films and Browning (Box 24)
  - Brownlow, Kevin (Box 24)
    - Clippings concerning various films (Box 24)
  - Bruckman, Clyde (Box 24)
    - Man on the Flying Trapeze., (see: Box 121) (Box 24)
  - Brusati, Franco (Box 24)
    - clippings concerning various films (Box 24)
  - Buechler, John (Box 24)
    - Trolls., press kit (Box 24)
  - Bunce, Alan (Box 24)
    - Babar: The Movie., press kit (Box 24)
  - Buñuel, Luis (Box 24)
    - L'Âge d'or (Age of Gold - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - El Ángel exterminador (The Exterminating Angel - U.S.)., notes, photographs, description, clippings (Box 24)
    - Cet obscur objet du désir (That Obscure Object of Desire - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 24)
    - Le Fantôme de la liberté., publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Los Olvidados (The Young and the Damned - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 24)
    - Robinson Crusoe., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 24)
    - Simón del desierto (Simon of the Desert - U.S.)., program, photographs, clippings (Box 24)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 24)
    - Notes and printed items concerning Buñuel (Box 24)
    - Clippings concerning Buñuel (Box 24)
  - Burge, Stuart (Box 25)
    - Othello., program, clippings (Box 25)
  - Burrows, James (Box 25)
    - Partners., notes, clippings (Box 25)
  - Burton, Tim (Box 25)
    - Batman., (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Batman Returns., clippings (Box 25)
    - Beetlejuice., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Ed Wood., press kit (Box 25)
    - Edward Scissorhands., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
    - Pee Wee's Big Adventure., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
  - Bute, Mary Ellen (Box 25)
    - Finnegan's Wake., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 25)
  - Butler, David (Box 25)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 25)
  - Butler, George and Robert Fiore (Box 25)
    - Pumping Iron (with Robert Fiore)., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
    - Pumping Iron II: The Women., publicity, clippings (Box 25)
  - Buzzell, Edward (Box 25)
    - At the Circus (aka A Day at the Circus)., photographs, clippings (Box 25)
  - Byrne, David (Box 25)
    - True Stories., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Clippings concerning Byrne (Box 25)
  - Byrum, John (Box 25)
    - Heart Beat., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Inserts., notes, fact sheet, clippings (Box 25)
    - The Razor's Edge., (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 25)
  - Caan, James (Box 25)
    - Hide in Plain Sight., notes, clippings (Box 25)
    - Clippings concerning Caan (Box 25)
  - Cacoyannis, Michael (Box 25)
    - A Girl in Black., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Iphigenia., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
    - Stella., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - The Trojan Women., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 25)
  - Cain, Christopher (Box 25)
    - The Stone Boy., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - That Was Then...This Is Now., clippings (Box 25)
  - Callow, Simon (Box 25)
    - The Ballad of the Sad Café., notes, program, publicity, clippings (Box 25)
  - Camp, Joe (Box 25)
    - Oh! Heavenly Dog., press kit, clippings (Box 25)
  - Capra, Frank (Box 25)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace., (see also: Box 113) (Box 25)
    - It Happened One Night., photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - It's a Wonderful Life., (see also: Box 113) (Box 25)
    - Lost Horizon., (see also: Box 113) (Box 25)
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town., printed item, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Mr. Smith Goes to Washington., (see also: Box 113) (Box 25)
    - You Can't Take it With You., (see also: Box 113) (Box 25)
    - Materials concerning other films and Capra, (see also: Box 113) (Box 25)
  - Cardiff, Jack (Box 25)
    - Sons and Lovers., notes, clippings (Box 25)
    - Materials concerning other films. (Box 25)
  - Carlino, Lewis John (Box 25)
    - The Great Santini., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
  - Carlsen, Henning (Box 25)
    - Människor möts och ljuv musik uppst âr i hjärtat (People Meet and Sweet Music Fills the Heart - U.S.)., publicity (Box 25)
    - Oviri (Wolf at the Door - U.S.)., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
    - Sult (Hunger - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 25)
  - Carné, Marcel (Box 25)
    - La Bible., program, publicity (Box 25)
    - Drôle de drame ou L'étrange aventure de Docteur Molyneux (Bizarre, Bizarre - U.S.)., (for hand-painted title on pressboard see: Box 121) (Box 25)
    - Les enfants du paradis (Children of Paradise - U.S.)., printed item, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Le Jour se Lève (Daybreak - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Le Quai des brumes (Port of Shadows - U.S.)., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Les Visiteurs du soir (The Devil's Envoys - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 25)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Carné (Box 25)
  - Caron, Glenn Gordon (Box 25)
    - Clean and Sober., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
  - Carpenter, John (Box 25)
    - Big Trouble in Little China., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
    - Escape From New York., press release, clippings (Box 25)
    - Halloween., notes, pressbook, clippings (Box 25)
    - Prince of Darkness., press kit, clippings (Box 25)
    - Starman., notes, statement from The American Humane Association, press kit, clippings (Box 25)
    - They Live., press kit, clippings (Box 25)
  - Carpenter, John (cont.) (Box 26)
    - The Thing., (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 26)
  - Carpi, Fabio (Box 26)
    - Il Quartetto Basileus (Basileus Quartet)., press kit, clippings (Box 26)
  - Casaril, Guy (Box 26)
    - Piaf., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 26)
  - Cass, Henry (Box 26)
    - Last Holiday., photographs, clippings (Box 26)
  - Cassavetes, John (Box 26)
    - Big Trouble., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 26)
    - Minnie and Moskowitz., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 26)
    - Husbands., (for publicity see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - Opening Night., notes, clippings (Box 26)
    - Shadows., notes, printed items, clippings (Box 26)
    - A Woman Under the Influence., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 26)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 26)
    - Notes, printed items and clippings concerning Cassavetes (Box 26)
  - Castellani, Renato (Box 26)
    - Du soldi di speranza (Two Cents Worth of Hope - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 26)
    - Romeo and Juliet., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 26)
  - Cates, Gilbert (Box 26)
    - I Never Sang for My Father., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 26)
    - Oh, God! Book II., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 26)
    - The Promise., notes, clippings (Box 26)
    - Clipping concerning: The Last Married Couple in America; printed item concerning Cates (Box 26)
  - Cavalcanti, Alberto, Charles Crichton, Basil Dearden, Robert Hamer (Box 26)
    - Dead of Night., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 26)
  - Chabrol, Claude (Box 26)
    - Les Bonne Femmes., notes, printed item, clippings (Box 26)
    - Le Boucher (The Butcher - U.S.)., press release, printed review, clippings (Box 26)
    - Les Cousins (The Cousins - U.S.)., notes, printed item, clippings (Box 26)
    - La Décade prodigieuse (Ten Days Wonder - U.S.)., press release, clippings (Box 26)
    - À double tour (Leda - U.S.)., notes, program notes, clippings (Box 26)
    - La Femme infidèle., notes, clippings (Box 26)
    - La Ligne de demarcation (Line of Demarcation - U.S.)., program notes (Box 26)
    - Une partie of plaisir (Pleasure Party - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 26)
    - Que la bête meure (This Man Must Die - U.S.)., publicity, program, clippings (Box 26)
    - Violette Nozièr., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 26)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 26)
    - Notes, press release and clippings concerning Chabrol (Box 26)
  - Champion, Gregg (Box 26)
    - Short Time., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 26)
  - Chaplin, Charles (Box 26)
    - The Countess from Hong Kong., (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - The Gold Rush., (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - The Great Dictator., (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - A King in New York., (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - Limelight., (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - Modern Times., (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - Shoulder Arms., photographs, clippings (Box 26)
    - A Woman of Paris., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 26)
    - Clippings concerning other films, (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
    - Publicity and clippings for My Autobiography, by Charles Chaplin (Box 26)
    - Notes, photograph and other printed items concerning other films and Chaplin (Box 26)
    - Clippings concerning Chaplin, (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
  - Chapman, Matthew (Box 26)
    - Strangers Kiss., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 26)
  - Chapman, Michael (Box 26)
    - All the Right Moves., publicity, clippings (Box 26)
    - Clan of the Cave Bear., (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Chenal, Pierre (Box 26)
    - Crime et châtiment (Crime and Punishment - U.S.)., photographs (Box 26)
  - Chong, Tommy (Box 26)
    - Cheech & Chong's The Corsican Brothers., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 26)
    - Cheech & Chong's Next Movie., notes, press kit, clipping (Box 26)
    - Up in Smoke., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 26)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 26)
  - Chopra, Joyce (Box 26)
    - Smooth Talk., notes, press release, clippings (Box 26)
  - Chukhrai, Grigori (Box 26)
    - Ballada o soldate (Ballad of a Soldier - U.S.)., program, printed item, clippings (Box 26)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 26)
  - Chytilová, Vera (Box 26)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 26)
  - Cimino, Michael (Box 26)
    - The Deer Hunter., (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Heaven's Gate., (3 folders) (see also: Box 113) (Box 26)
  - Cimino, Michael (cont.) (Box 27)
    - The Sicilian., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 27)
    - Year of the Dragon., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 27)
    - Notes and clippings concerning Cimino (Box 27)
  - Clair, René (Box 27)
    - À nous la liberté (Liberty for Us - U.S.)., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - La Beauté du diable (Beauty and the Devil - U.S.)., publicity, program, photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - Un chapeau de paille d'Italie (An Italian Straw Hat - U.S.)., notes, related printed items, photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - The Ghost Goes West., photographs (Box 27)
    - Porte des Lilas (Gates of Paris - U.S.)., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - Sous les toits de Paris., (see: Box 113) (Box 27)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 27)
    - Clippings and other printed items concerning Clair, (see also: Box 113) (Box 27)
  - Clark, Bob (Box 27)
    - Murder by Decree., (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Rhinestone., (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Trubute., notes, publicity, photographs, printed item, clippings (Box 27)
    - Turk 182!, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 27)
  - Clavell, James (Box 27)
    - Clippings concerning various films and Clavell (Box 27)
  - Clayton, Jack (Box 27)
    - The Great Gatsby., (see also: Box 113) (Box 27)
    - The Innocents., notes, clippings (Box 27)
    - The Lonely Passion of Judith Hearne., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 27)
    - Our Mother's House., notes, cast list, clippings (Box 27)
    - The Pumpkin Eater., clippings (Box 27)
    - Room at the Top., notes, program notes, clippings (Box 27)
    - Something Wicked This Way Comes., (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Clement, Dick (Box 27)
    - Clippings concerning various films (Box 27)
  - Clément, René (Box 27)
    - Jeux interdits (Forbidden Games - U.S.)., (see also: Box 113) (Box 27)
    - Monsieur Ripois (Lover Boy - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - La Mura di Malapaga (The Walls of Malapaga - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 27)
    - Plein soleil (Purple Noon - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 27)
    - This Angry Age., photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - clippings concerning other films and Clément (Box 27)
  - Clements, Ron (Box 27)
    - The Great Mouse Detective., press kit, clippings (Box 27)
  - Clements, Ron and John Musker (Box 27)
    - The Little Mermaid., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 27)
  - Clifford, Graeme (Box 27)
    - Frances., (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Gleaming the Tube., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 27)
  - Cline, Edward F. (Box 27)
    - The Bank Dick., photographs (Box 27)
    - Million Dollar Legs., photographs (Box 27)
    - My Little Chickadee., photographs (Box 27)
    - Never Give a Sucker an Even Break., photographs (Box 27)
  - Clouse, Robert (Box 27)
    - The Big Brawl., press kit, clippings (Box 27)
    - Enter the Dragon., notes, clippings (Box 27)
  - Clouzot, Henrí (Box 27)
    - Le Mystère Picasso (The Mystery of Picasso - U.S.)., notes, photographs, printed items, clippings (Box 27)
    - Le Salaire de la peur (The Wages of Fear - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 27)
    - La Vérité (The Truth - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Clouzot (Box 27)
  - Clurman, Harold (Box 27)
    - deadline at Dawn., photographs (Box 27)
  - Cocteau, Jean (Box 27)
    - L'Aigle à deux têtes (The Eagle With Two Heads - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 27)
    - La Belle et la bête (Beauty and the Beast - U.S.)., printed item, program, postcard, clippings (Box 27)
    - Orphée (Orpheus - U.S.)., (see also: Box 113) (Box 27)
    - Les Parents terribles (The Storm Within - U.S.)., (see also: Box 113) (Box 27)
    - Le Sang d'un poète (The Blood of a Poet - U.S.)., notes, printed items, clippings (Box 27)
    - Le Testament d'Orphèe, ou ne me demandez pas pourquoi! (The Testament of Orpheus - U.S.)., (see also: Box 113) (Box 27)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Cocteau, (see also: Box 113) (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous items concerning Cocteau (Box 27)
  - Coen, Joel and Ethan (Box 28)
    - Blood Simple., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 28)
    - Miller's Crossing., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 28)
    - Raising Arizona., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 28)
    - Clipping concerning the Coens (Box 28)
  - Cohen, Annette, et al. (Box 28)
    - Love., press release, clippings (Box 28)
  - Cohen, Larry (Box 28)
    - Bone., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 28)
    - The Private Files of J. Edgar Hoover., press release, clippings (Box 28)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 28)
    - Clippings and press release concerning Cohen (Box 28)
  - Cohen, Rob (Box 28)
    - Clippings concerning various films and Cohen (Box 28)
  - Coleman, Graham (Box 28)
    - Tibet: A Buddhist Trilogy., press kit (Box 28)
  - Collinson, Peter (Box 28)
    - Innocent Bystanders., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 28)
    - The Penthouse., publicity, clippings (Box 28)
    - clippings concerning other films (Box 28)
  - Colpi, Henri (Box 28)
    - Clipping concerning various films (Box 28)
  - Columbus, Chris (Box 28)
    - Adventures in Babysitting., press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 28)
    - Heartbreak Hotel., press kit, clippings (Box 28)
  - Comencini, Luigi (Box 28)
    - The Sunday Woman., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 28)
    - Clippings and printed item concerning other films and Comencini (Box 28)
  - Condon, Bill (Box 28)
    - Gods and Monsters., publicity (Box 28)
  - Cook, Fielder (Box 28)
    - How to Save a Marriage—And Ruin Your Life., publicity, clippings (Box 28)
    - Too Far To Go., press kit, clippings (Box 28)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 28)
  - Coolidge, Martha (Box 28)
    - Joy of Sex., press release, clippings (Box 28)
    - Valley Girl., notes, press release, clippings (Box 28)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 28)
  - Coppola, Francis Ford (Box 28)
    - Apocalypse Now., (3 folders) (Box 28)
    - Captain EO., photographs (Box 28)
    - The Conversation., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 28)
    - The Cotton Club., (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Finian's Rainbow., notes, clippings (Box 28)